Guide to the William Benton Papers 1839-1973
University of Chicago Library
- Series I: General Files
  - Subseries 1: Personal Life
    - Sub-subseries 5: Travel Files
      - Turkish coast cruise yachting party, M-Z (Box 62, Folder 3)
      - Turkish coast cruise 1971, general (Box 62, Folder 4)
      - Turkish coast cruise 1971, finance (Box 62, Folder 5)
      - Turkish coast cruise 1971, resource file (Box 62, Folder 6)
      - Turkish coast cruise 1971, itinerary (Box 62, Folder 7)
      - Turkish coast cruise 1971, yachting party, general (Box 62, Folder 8)
      - Turkish coast cruise 1971, yachting party, guests (Box 62, Folder 9)
      - Yachts, 1963-1967 (Box 63, Folder 1)
      - Yachts, 1968-1972 (Box 63, Folder 2)
      - Yachts, Doxiadis, 1969 (Box 63, Folder 3)
      - Yachts, Tritona, 1958 (Box 63, Folder 4)
  - Subseries 2: General Correspondence
    - Sub-subseries 1: 1930-1940
      - A, general (Box 64, Folder 1)
      - B, general (Box 64, Folder 2)
      - Bowles, Chester, 1936-1937 (Box 64, Folder 3)
      - Bowles, 1938 (Box 64, Folder 4)
      - Bowles, 1939 (Box 64, Folder 5)
      - Bowles, 1940 (Box 64, Folder 6)
      - Brown, Lewis, 1937-1940 (Box 64, Folder 7)
      - C, general (Box 64, Folder 8)
      - Childs, Helen, 1939 (Box 64, Folder 9)
      - D, general (Box 64, Folder 10)
      - Delacorte, George, 1935-1940 (Box 64, Folder 11)
      - E-F, general (Box 64, Folder 12)
      - G, general (Box 64, Folder 13)
      - Goldstein, Robert, 1936-1940 (Box 64, Folder 14)
      - Ha-Hi, general (Box 65, Folder 1)
      - Hale, E. V., 1938-1941 (Box 65, Folder 2)
      - Hartwell, Jobson and Kibber, 1940 (Box 65, Folder 3)
      - Ho-Hz, general (Box 65, Folder 4)
      - Hurd, Arthur M., 1940 (Box 65, Folder 5)
      - I, general (Box 65, Folder 6)
      - J, general (Box 65, Folder 7)
      - K, general (Box 65, Folder 8)
      - L, general (Box 65, Folder 9)
      - LaFollette, Philip, 1937-1939 (Box 65, Folder 10)
      - LaFollette, 1940 (Box 65, Folder 11)
      - LaFollette, Robert M., 1937-1940 (Box 65, Folder 12)
      - Lasswell, Harold D., 1936-1940 (Box 65, Folder 13)
      - Lemmon, Guy, 1935-1940 (Box 65, Folder 14)
      - Little, Edward H., 1939-1940 (Box 65, Folder 15)
      - Luce, Henry R., 1938-1939 (Box 65, Folder 16)
      - Lyon, George H., 1940 (Box 65, Folder 17)
      - M, general (Box 66, Folder 1)
      - Marsh, Reginald, 1939-1940 (Box 66, Folder 2)
      - Merrill, Charles, 1936-1939 (Box 66, Folder 3)
      - Na-No, general (Box 66, Folder 4)
      - Needham, Maurice H., 1936-1937 (Box 66, Folder 5)
      - O-Q, general (Box 66, Folder 6)
      - R, general (Box 66, Folder 7)
      - Rochford, Daniel, 1938-1940 (Box 66, Folder 8)
      - Rubicam, Raymond, 1936-1940 (Box 66, Folder 9)
      - Ruhm, Herman, 1937-1940 (Box 66, Folder 10)
      - Ryan, T. L., 1938-1940 (Box 66, Folder 11)
      - S, general (Box 66, Folder 12)
      - Schleiter, Walter B., 1935-1940 (Box 66, Folder 13)
      - Strauss, Helen (Box 66, Folder 14)
      - T, general (Box 67, Folder 1)
      - Tallman, Bertha, 1940 (Box 67, Folder 2)
      - Thurston, Lorrin P., 1937-1940 (Box 67, Folder 3)
      - Time, Inc., 1936-1940 (Box 67, Folder 4)
      - Tracey, Eugene A., 1937-1940 (Box 67, Folder 5)
      - U-V, general (Box 67, Folder 6)
      - Van Meter, Galen, 1933-1936 (Box 67, Folder 7)
      - Van Meter, 1937-1940 (Box 67, Folder 8)
      - W, general (Box 67, Folder 9)
      - Wattley, Joan, 1940 (Box 67, Folder 10)
      - X-Z, general (Box 67, Folder 11)
      - Yale University, 1931-1940 (Box 67, Folder 12)
      - Young, James W., 1936-1939 (Box 67, Folder 13)
      - Young, John O., 1936-1940 (Box 67, Folder 14)
    - Sub-subseries 2: 1941-1947
      - A, general (Box 68, Folder 1)
      - Ba-Be, general (Box 68, Folder 2)
      - Barton, Bruce, 1941-1947 (Box 68, Folder 3)
      - Bell, Laird, 1944-1947 (Box 68, Folder 4)
      - Bi-Bri, general (Box 68, Folder 5)
      - Bingham, Alfred, 1942-1947 (Box 68, Folder 6)
      - Birk, Louis, 1945 (Box 68, Folder 7)
      - Bowles, Chester, 1941 (Box 69, Folder 1)
      - Bowles, 1942 (Box 69, Folder 2)
      - Bowles, 1943 (Box 69, Folder 3)
      - Bowles, 1944 (Box 69, Folder 4)
      - Bowles, 1945 (Box 69, Folder 5)
      - Bowles, 1946 (Box 69, Folder 6)
      - Bowles, Jan.-June 1947 (Box 69, Folder 7)
      - Bowles, July-Dec. 1947 (Box 69, Folder 8)
      - British Museum proposal, 1940-1941 (Box 70, Folder 1)
      - Bro-Bz, general (Box 70, Folder 2)
      - Brown, Lewis H., 1943-1946 (Box 70, Folder 3)
      - Buchbinder, Hazel, 1944-1945 (Box 70, Folder 4)
      - Buck, Pearl S., 1944-1947 (Box 70, Folder 5)
      - Burns, Robert K., 1944-1945 (Box 70, Folder 6)
      - Bye, George T., 1942-1944 (Box 70, Folder 7)
      - C, general (Box 71, Folder 1)
      - Cheyfitz, Edward (Box 71, Folder 2)
      - Cole, A. L., 1942-1947 (Box 71, Folder 3)
      - Colgate, S. Bayard, 1941-1947 (Box 71, Folder 4)
      - Cowles, Gardner, 1944-1945 (Box 71, Folder 5)
      - Coyle, Joanne, 1942-1943 (Box 71, Folder 6)
      - D, general (Box 71, Folder 7)
      - David, Donald, 1944-1945 (Box 71, Folder 8)
      - Davis, Smith, 1942-1947 (Box 71, Folder 9)
      - Delacorte, George, Jr., 1941-1945 (Box 71, Folder 10)
      - Dodd, John, 1943-1945 (Box 71, Folder 11)
      - R. R. Donnelley and Sons, 1945-1947 (Box 71, Folder 12)
      - E, general (Box 71, Folder 13)
      - Emmerich, Herbert, 1944-1945 (Box 71, Folder 14)
      - F, general (Box 72, Folder 1)
      - Field, Marshall, 1942-1947 (Box 72, Folder 2)
      - Fizdale, Tom, 1941-1945 (Box 72, Folder 3)
      - Fly, James Lawrence, 1941-1945 (Box 72, Folder 4)
      - Francisco, Don, 1941-1946 (Box 72, Folder 5)
      - Ga-Gl, general (Box 72, Folder 6)
      - Gager, Curt, 1940-1947 (Box 72, Folder 7)
      - Galbraith, J. Kenneth, 1944-1945 (Box 72, Folder 8)
      - Go-Gz, general (Box 72, Folder 9)
      - Goldstein, Robert, 1941-1947 (Box 72, Folder 10)
      - Gould, Bruce, 1945-1947 (Box 72, Folder 11)
      - Gould, Jay, 1941-1947 (Box 72, Folder 12)
      - Guinness, Arthur, 1941-1947 (Box 72, Folder 13)
      - Ha-Hi, general (Box 73, Folder 1)
      - Hale, Edward V., 1941-1947 (Box 73, Folder 2)
      - Hard, William, 1944-1946 (Box 73, Folder 3)
      - Harrison, Wallace K., 1941-1947 (Box 73, Folder 4)
      - Ho-Hz, general (Box 73, Folder 5)
      - Hoffman, Paul, 1941-1947 (Box 73, Folder 6)
      - Hormel, Jay, 1944-1947 (Box 73, Folder 7)
      - Hutchinson, Paul, 1944-1947 (Box 73, Folder 8)
      - I, general (Box 73, Folder 9)
      - Ingersoll, Ralph and Elaine, 1941-1947 (Box 73, Folder 10)
      - J, general (Box 73, Folder 11)
      - Janeway, Eliot, 1944-1945 (Box 73, Folder 12)
      - Jessup, John K., 1944 (Box 73, Folder 13)
      - Johnson, Robert L., 1941-1945 (Box 74, Folder 1)
      - Johnston, Eric A., 1943-1947 (Box 74, Folder 2)
      - Jones, Owen, 1943-1946 (Box 74, Folder 3)
      - Ka-Ke, general (Box 74, Folder 4)
      - Kanzler, Ernest, 1945 (Box 74, Folder 5)
      - Kauffmann-Grinstead, Dr. Kurt, 1941-1945 (Box 74, Folder 6)
      - Kaye, Sydney M., 1942-1944 (Box 74, Folder 7)
      - Keiffer, Elaine Brown, 1943-1945 (Box 74, Folder 8)
      - Kesten, Paul W., 1944-1945 (Box 74, Folder 9)
      - Ki-Kz, general (Box 74, Folder 10)
      - Krause, William W., 1941-1943 (Box 74, Folder 11)
      - La, general (Box 74, Folder 12)
      - LaFollette, Philip F., 1941-1947 (Box 74, Folder 13)
      - LaFollette, Robert M., 1941-1947 (Box 74, Folder 14)
      - LaRoche, Chester, 1942-1947 (Box 74, Folder 15)
      - Lasswell, Harold, 1941-1944 (Box 75, Folder 1)
      - Lasswell, 1945-1947 (Box 75, Folder 2)
      - Le, general (Box 75, Folder 3)
      - Leffingwell, R. C., 1944-1945 (Box 75, Folder 4)
      - Lemmon, Guy, 1941-1947 (Box 75, Folder 5)
      - Levi, Edward H., 1944-1945 (Box 75, Folder 6)
      - Lf-Lz, general (Box 75, Folder 7)
      - Lindbergh, Charles, 1941-1947 (Box 75, Folder 8)
      - Logan, Harlan, 1944-1947 (Box 75, Folder 9)
      - Lovenstein, Meno (Box 75, Folder 10)
      - Luce, Clare Booth, 1941-1947 (Box 75, Folder 11)
      - Luce, Henry R., 1941-1947 (Box 75, Folder 12)
      - Ma, general (Box 76, Folder 1)
      - Maverick, Maury, 1944-1947 (Box 76, Folder 2)
      - Mazur, Paul, 1941-1942 (Box 76, Folder 3)
      - Mc, general (Box 76, Folder 4)
      - McCormick, Robert, 1941-1946 (Box 76, Folder 5)
      - Me-Mi, general (Box 76, Folder 6)
      - Miller, Allan, 1941-1947 (Box 76, Folder 7)
      - Mo-Mz, general (Box 76, Folder 8)
      - Montague, Gilbert, 1944-1946 (Box 76, Folder 9)
      - Montgomery, Douglass, 1941-1942 (Box 76, Folder 10)
      - Moore, Ray W., 1942-1947 (Box 76, Folder 11)
      - Motley, Arthur H., 1944-1947 (Box 76, Folder 12)
      - Muldowney, Silvester, 1941-1947 (Box 76, Folder 13)
      - N-O, general (Box 76, Folder 14)
      - National Committee on Maternal Health, Inc., 1942 (Box 77, Folder 1)
      - Nichols, William, 1945-1947 (Box 77, Folder 2)
      - O'Brien, Philip, 1945-1947 (Box 77, Folder 3)
      - Pa, general (Box 77, Folder 4)
      - Patton, James G., 1945-1947 (Box 77, Folder 5)
      - Paul's Tax Proposals, 1942 (Box 77, Folder 6)
      - Pe-Q, general (Box 77, Folder 7)
      - Porter, Paul A., 1946-1947 (Box 77, Folder 8)
      - Pritchard, Edward, 1944-1945 (Box 77, Folder 9)
      - Ra-Ri, general (Box 77, Folder 10)
      - Revere, Tom, 1941-1947 (Box 77, Folder 11)
      - Richardson, H. Smith, 1941-1942 (Box 77, Folder 12)
      - Ro-Rz, general (Box 78, Folder 1)
      - Rochford, Daniel, 1941-1945 (Box 78, Folder 2)
      - Rockfeller, David, John, Laurance, Nelson, 1941-1947 (Box 78, Folder 3)
      - Rogers, James, 1941-1946 (Box 78, Folder 4)
      - Rosenberg, Anna, 1941-1947 (Box 78, Folder 5)
      - Rubicam, Raymond, 1941-1947 (Box 78, Folder 6)
      - Ruhm, Herman D., 1941-1947 (Box 78, Folder 7)
      - Ruml, Beardsley, 1941-1947 (Box 78, Folder 8)
      - Sa-Sk, general (Box 78, Folder 9)
      - Scherman, Harry, 1941-1946 (Box 78, Folder 10)
      - Schuster, M. Lincoln (Max), 1941-1946 (Box 78, Folder 11)
      - Schleiter, Walter, 1941-1947 (Box 78, Folder 12)
      - Shaw, Alejandro, 1944-1946 (Box 79, Folder 1)
      - Shaw, Arch W., 1944-1947 (Box 79, Folder 2)
      - Sheperdson, William, 1945 (Box 79, Folder 3)
      - Shubart, Harry E., 1942-1947 (Box 79, Folder 4)
      - Siepman, Charles, 1944-1946 (Box 79, Folder 5)
      - Sl-Sp, general (Box 79, Folder 6)
      - St-Sz, general (Box 79, Folder 7)
      - Stebbins, Frances F., 1943-1947 (Box 79, Folder 8)
      - Sterling, John C., 1947 (Box 79, Folder 9)
      - T, general (Box 79, Folder 10)
      - Tallman, Bertha, 1941-1942 (Box 79, Folder 11)
      - Taylor, Howard C., 1942-1946 (Box 79, Folder 12)
      - Thomas, Norman, 1942-1945 (Box 79, Folder 13)
      - Thurston, Lorrin P., 1941-1945 (Box 79, Folder 14)
      - Tracey, Eugene A., 1941-1947 (Box 79, Folder 15)
      - Trammell, Niles, 1941-1947 (Box 79, Folder 16)
      - U-V, general (Box 80, Folder 1)
      - Van Meter, Galen, 1941-1944 (Box 80, Folder 2)
      - Van Meter, 1945-1947 (Box 80, Folder 3)
      - Vansittart, Lord, 1943-1945 (Box 80, Folder 4)
      - Vogel, Frank, 1941-1947 (Box 80, Folder 5)
      - Wa, general (Box 80, Folder 6)
      - Wallace, DeWitt, 1941-1947 (Box 80, Folder 7)
      - Walsh, J. Raymond, 1944-1947 (Box 80, Folder 8)
      - Wanger, Walter F., 1941-1947 (Box 80, Folder 9)
      - Warren, Lingan A., 1944-1945 (Box 80, Folder 10)
      - War-related correspondence, general (Box 80, Folder 11)
      - We, general (Box 80, Folder 12)
      - Wh, general (Box 80, Folder 13)
      - White, Thomas J., 1941-1944 (Box 80, Folder 14)
      - Wi, general (Box 80, Folder 15)
      - Wo-Wr, general (Box 81, Folder 1)
      - Wood, Gen. Robert E., 1941-1947 (Box 81, Folder 2)
      - X-Z, general (Box 81, Folder 3)
      - Young, James W., 1941-1947 (Box 81, Folder 4)
      - Zimmerman, Herbert P., 1942-1947 (Box 81, Folder 5)
      - Zurcher, Arnold J., 1945 (Box 81, Folder 6)
    - Sub-subseries 3: 1948-1957
      - Aa-Ad, general (Box 82, Folder 1)
      - Adams, Taylor, 1947-1956 (Box 82, Folder 2)
      - Adler, Mortimer, 1948-1950 (Box 82, Folder 3)
      - Adler, 1951-1957 (Box 82, Folder 4)
      - Ag-Ai, general (Box 82, Folder 5)
      - Al, general (Box 82, Folder 6)
      - Allen, C. Stanley, 1951-1954 (Box 82, Folder 7)
      - Allen, 1955-1957 (Box 82, Folder 8)
      - Altschul, Frank, 1950-1957 (Box 82, Folder 9)
      - Am, general (Box 83, Folder 1)
      - American Assembly, 1957 (Box 83, Folder 2)
      - American Association for the United Nations, 1950-1957 (Box 83, Folder 3)
      - American Civil Liberties Union, 1949-1957 (Box 83, Folder 4)
      - American Committee on United Europe, 1956-1957 (Box 83, Folder 5)
      - American Foreign Service Association, 1947-1956 (Box 83, Folder 6)
      - American Heritage Foundation, 1956-1957 (Box 83, Folder 7)
      - American Political Science Association (Box 83, Folder 8)
      - An, general (Box 84, Folder 1)
      - Ap-Ar, general (Box 84, Folder 2)
      - Ascoli, Max, 1949-1954 (Box 84, Folder 3)
      - As-Az, general (Box 84, Folder 4)
      - Ba-Ban, general (Box 84, Folder 5)
      - Balch, Richard, 1950-1957 (Box 84, Folder 6)
      - Bar, general (Box 84, Folder 7)
      - Baron, Sydney, 1956-1957 (Box 84, Folder 8)
      - Barton, Bruce, 1949-1957 (Box 84, Folder 9)
      - Bas-Baz, general (Box 85, Folder 1)
      - Bea-Bel, general (Box 85, Folder 2)
      - Ben-Bez, general (Box 85, Folder 3)
      - Berkson, Seymour, 1948-1956 (Box 85, Folder 4)
      - Bh-Bj, general (Box 85, Folder 5)
      - Bimson, Walter R., 1948-1957 (Box 85, Folder 6)
      - Bl, general (Box 85, Folder 7)
      - Bo, general (Box 85, Folder 8)
      - Bowles, Chester, Jan.-June 1948 (Box 86, Folder 1)
      - Bowles, July-Dec. 1948 (Box 86, Folder 2)
      - Bowles, 1949 (Box 86, Folder 3)
      - Bowles, 1950 (Box 86, Folder 4)
      - Bowles, Jan.-June 1951 (Box 86, Folder 5)
      - Bowles, July-Dec. 1951 (Box 86, Folder 6)
      - Bowles, Jan.-June 1952 (Box 86, Folder 7)
      - Bowles, July-Dec. 1952 (Box 86, Folder 8)
      - Bowles, 1953 (Box 87, Folder 1)
      - Bowles, 1954 (Box 87, Folder 2)
      - Bowles, Tibetan scroll (Box 87, Folder 3)
      - Bowles, 1955 (Box 87, Folder 4)
      - Bowles, 1956 (Box 87, Folder 5)
      - Bowles, Jan.-June 1957 (Box 87, Folder 6)
      - Bowles, July-Dec. 1957 (Box 87, Folder 7)
      - Br-Bz, general, #1 (Box 88, Folder 1)
      - Br-Bz, #2 (Box 88, Folder 2)
      - Br-Bz, #3 (Box 88, Folder 3)
      - Br-Bz, #4 (Box 88, Folder 4)
      - Br-Bz, #5 (Box 88, Folder 5)
      - Br-Bz, #6 (Box 88, Folder 6)
      - Braden, Spruille (Box 88, Folder 7)
      - Brown, Sevelon (Box 88, Folder 8)
      - Ca-Ce, general, #1 (Box 89, Folder 1)
      - Ca-Ce, #2 (Box 89, Folder 2)
      - Ca-Ce, #3 (Box 89, Folder 3)
      - Ca-Ce, #4 (Box 89, Folder 4)
      - Canham, Erwin D. (Box 89, Folder 5)
      - Carleton College, 1948-1949 (Box 90, Folder 1)
      - Carleton College, 1950-1952 (Box 90, Folder 2)
      - Carleton College, 1953 (Box 90, Folder 3)
      - Carleton College, 1954 (Box 90, Folder 4)
      - Carleton College, 1955 (Box 90, Folder 5)
      - Carleton College, 1956-1957 (Box 90, Folder 6)
      - Cavers, David (Box 90, Folder 7)
      - Cerf, Jay (Box 90, Folder 8)
      - Ch-Ci, general (Box 90, Folder 9)
      - Chafee, Zechariah (Box 90, Folder 10)
      - Charles, Joseph (Box 91, Folder 1)
      - Chevalier, Willard (Box 91, Folder 2)
      - Childs, Marquis (Box 91, Folder 3)
      - Cl, general (Box 91, Folder 4)
      - Clark, Cameron (Box 91, Folder 5)
      - Clark, William (Box 91, Folder 6)
      - Clayton, William L. (Box 91, Folder 7)
      - Co, general, #1 (Box 91, Folder 8)
      - Co, #2 (Box 91, Folder 9)
      - Co, #3 (Box 91, Folder 10)
      - Co, #4 (Box 91, Folder 11)
      - Co, #5 (Box 91, Folder 12)
      - Cohn, Dr. Alfred E. (Box 92, Folder 1)
      - Colgate, S. Bayard (Box 92, Folder 2)
      - Council on Foreign Relations (Chicago) (Box 92, Folder 3)
      - Council on Foreign Relations (New York) (Box 92, Folder 4)
      - Council on World Affairs (Box 92, Folder 5)
      - Cousins, Norman (Box 92, Folder 6)
      - Cr-Cz, general (Box 92, Folder 7)
      - Cronin, Anne, 1956 (Box 92, Folder 8)
      - Cronin, Jan.-May 1957 (Box 92, Folder 9)
      - Cronin, June-Dec. 1957 (Box 92, Folder 10)
      - Crowther, Geoffrey (Box 92, Folder 11)
      - Da-De, general, #1 (Box 93, Folder 1)
      - Da-De, #2 (Box 93, Folder 2)
      - David, Donald K. (Box 93, Folder 3)
      - Davis, A. M. (Box 93, Folder 4)
      - Delacorte, George (Box 93, Folder 5)
      - Di-Do, general (Box 93, Folder 6)
      - Donovan, William J. (Box 93, Folder 7)
      - Dr-Dz, general, #1 (Box 93, Folder 8)
      - Dr-Dz, #2 (Box 93, Folder 9)
      - Dulles, John Foster (Box 93, Folder 10)
      - E, general, #1 (Box 94, Folder 1)
      - E, #2 (Box 94, Folder 2)
      - Eisenhower, Milton (Box 94, Folder 3)
      - Eisenhower Exchange Fellowships (Box 94, Folder 4)
      - Ernst, Morris L. (Box 94, Folder 5)
      - Ethridge, Mark (Box 94, Folder 6)
      - Eurich, Alvin C. (Box 94, Folder 7)
      - Evans, Luther (Box 94, Folder 8)
      - Fa-Fl, general, #1 (Box 95, Folder 1)
      - Fa-Fl, #2 (Box 95, Folder 2)
      - Faust, Clarence (Box 95, Folder 3)
      - Ferry, W. H. (Ping) (Box 95, Folder 4)
      - Field, Marshall (Box 95, Folder 5)
      - Finkelstein, Louis (Box 95, Folder 6)
      - Finletter, Thomas (Box 95, Folder 7)
      - Fletcher, C. Scott (Box 95, Folder 8)
      - Flynn, Catherine (Box 95, Folder 9)
      - Fo-Fz, general, #1 (Box 96, Folder 1)
      - Fo-Fz, #2 (Box 96, Folder 2)
      - Folsom, Marion (Box 96, Folder 3)
      - Ford, Henry (Box 96, Folder 4)
      - Foster, William C. (Box 96, Folder 5)
      - Frances, Clarence (Box 96, Folder 6)
      - Ga, general, #1 (Box 96, Folder 7)
      - Ga, #2 (Box 96, Folder 8)
      - Gager, Curtis H. (Box 96, Folder 9)
      - Gi-Go, general (Box 96, Folder 10)
      - Goldstein, Robert (Box 96, Folder 11)
      - Gould, Bruce, 1948-1952 (Box 97, Folder 1)
      - Gould, 1953-1957 (Box 97, Folder 2)
      - Gould, Jay (Box 97, Folder 3)
      - Gr-Gz, general, #1 (Box 97, Folder 4)
      - Gr-Gz, #2 (Box 97, Folder 5)
      - Graebner, Walter (Box 97, Folder 6)
      - Greenfield, Edward (Box 97, Folder 7)
      - Griswold, A. Whitney (Box 97, Folder 8)
      - Guinness, Arthur (Box 97, Folder 9)
      - Ha, general, #1 (Box 98, Folder 1)
      - Ha, #2 (Box 98, Folder 2)
      - Hale, Edward V. (Box 98, Folder 3)
      - Hardman, David, 1948-1957 (Box 98, Folder 4)
      - Hardman, 1953-1957 (Box 98, Folder 5)
      - Haydon, Brownlee (Box 98, Folder 6)
      - He-Hi, general, #1 (Box 98, Folder 7)
      - He-Hi, #2 (Box 98, Folder 8)
      - Hecht, George J. (Box 98, Folder 9)
      - Hicks, Orton H. (Box 98, Folder 10)
      - Ho, general, #1 (Box 99, Folder 1)
      - Ho, #2 (Box 99, Folder 2)
      - Hoffman, Michael L. (Box 99, Folder 3)
      - Hoffman, Paul G., 1948-1949 (Box 99, Folder 4)
      - Hoffman, 1950-1952 (Box 99, Folder 5)
      - Hoffman, 1953-1954 (Box 99, Folder 6)
      - Hoffman, 1956-1957 (Box 99, Folder 7)
      - Holland, Kenneth (Box 99, Folder 8)
      - Hormel, Jay (Box 99, Folder 9)
      - Hu-Hz, general (Box 100, Folder 1)
      - Hutchins, Robert M., 1948-1952 (Box 100, Folder 2)
      - Hutchins, 1953 (Box 100, Folder 3)
      - Hutchins, Jan.-June 1954 (Box 100, Folder 4)
      - Hutchins, July-Dec. 1954 (Box 100, Folder 5)
      - Hutchins, Jan.-April 1956 (Box 100, Folder 6)
      - Hutchins, May-Dec. 1956 (Box 100, Folder 7)
      - Hutchins, Jan.-June 1957 (Box 100, Folder 8)
      - Hutchins, July-Dec. 1957 (Box 100, Folder 9)
      - Hutchinson, Paul (Box 100, Folder 10)
      - Hyde, Anthony (Box 100, Folder 11)
      - I, general (Box 101, Folder 1)
      - Ingersoll, Ralph (Box 101, Folder 2)
      - International Trade Organization (Box 101, Folder 3)
      - J, general (Box 101, Folder 4)
      - Jacoby, Neil (Box 101, Folder 5)
      - Jessup, John K. (Box 101, Folder 6)
      - Johnston, Eric (Box 101, Folder 7)
      - Joyce, Jean (Box 101, Folder 8)
      - Joyce, William H. (Box 101, Folder 9)
      - Ka-Ke, general, #1 (Box 101, Folder 10)
      - Ka-Ke, #2 (Box 101, Folder 11)
      - Ki-Kl, general (Box 102, Folder 1)
      - King-Hall, Stephen (Box 102, Folder 2)
      - Kintner, Robert (Box 102, Folder 3)
      - Kl-Kz, general (Box 102, Folder 4)
      - La, general (Box 102, Folder 5)
      - LaFollette, Isen, Philip, Robert (Box 102, Folder 6)
      - LaRoche, Chester J., 1948-1950 (Box 102, Folder 7)
      - LaRoche, 1951-1957 (Box 102, Folder 8)
      - Larsen, Roy E. (Box 102, Folder 9)
      - Lasswell, Harold, 1948-1950 (Box 102, Folder 10)
      - Lasswell, 1951-1952 (Box 103, Folder 1)
      - Lasswell, 1953-1954 (Box 103, Folder 2)
      - Lasswell, 1956-1957 (Box 103, Folder 3)
      - Lazarus, Fred (Box 103, Folder 4)
      - Le, general (Box 103, Folder 5)
      - Levine, Joshua (Box 103, Folder 6)
      - Levitan, David M. (Box 103, Folder 7)
      - Li-Lo, general (Box 103, Folder 8)
      - Lu-Lz, general (Box 103, Folder 9)
      - Luce, Clare Booth (Box 103, Folder 10)
      - Luce, Henry (Box 103, Folder 11)
      - Ma-Mar, general (Box 104, Folder 1)
      - MacLeish, Archibald (Box 104, Folder 2)
      - Markel, Lester (Box 104, Folder 3)
      - Martin, Harry (Box 104, Folder 4)
      - Mas-Maz, general (Box 104, Folder 5)
      - Mayer, Milton (Box 104, Folder 6)
      - Mc, general, #1 (Box 104, Folder 7)
      - Mc, #2 (Box 104, Folder 8)
      - McCabe, Thomas B. (Box 104, Folder 9)
      - Me, general (Box 105, Folder 1)
      - Means, Gardiner (Box 105, Folder 2)
      - Merrill, Charles (Box 105, Folder 3)
      - Meynell, Alix (Box 105, Folder 4)
      - Mi, general (Box 105, Folder 5)
      - Mo, general, #1 (Box 105, Folder 6)
      - Mo, #2 (Box 105, Folder 7)
      - Mu-Mz, general (Box 105, Folder 8)
      - Na, general (Box 105, Folder 9)
      - Ne, general (Box 105, Folder 10)
      - Ni, general (Box 106, Folder 1)
      - Nichols, William (Box 106, Folder 2)
      - No-Nz, general (Box 106, Folder 3)
      - Nuveen, John (Box 106, Folder 4)
      - O, general (Box 106, Folder 5)
      - O'Meara, Walter (Box 106, Folder 6)
      - Pa, general (Box 106, Folder 7)
      - Pe-Pf, general (Box 106, Folder 8)
      - Ph, general (Box 106, Folder 9)
      - Pilgrims of the U. S. (Box 106, Folder 10)
      - Pioda, Mary Emma, Apr.-Sept. 1955 (Box 106, Folder 11)
      - Pioda, Sept.-Dec. 1955 (Box 106, Folder 12)
      - Po, general (Box 107, Folder 1)
      - Porter, Paul (Box 107, Folder 2)
      - Pr-Pz, general (Box 107, Folder 3)
      - Ra, general (Box 107, Folder 4)
      - Randall, Clarence (Box 107, Folder 5)
      - Rather, Victor (Box 107, Folder 6)
      - Re, general (Box 107, Folder 7)
      - Reed, Philip (Box 107, Folder 8)
      - Reid, Ogden (Box 107, Folder 9)
      - Reuther, Walter (Box 107, Folder 10)
      - Ri, general (Box 107, Folder 11)
      - Roa-Rol, general (Box 108, Folder 1)
      - Rockefeller, Nelson (Box 108, Folder 2)
      - Rollins College (Box 108, Folder 3)
      - Rom-Roz (Box 108, Folder 4)
      - Romulo, Carlos (Box 108, Folder 5)
      - Rosenberg, Anna, 1948-1949 (Box 108, Folder 6)
      - Rosenberg, 1950-1952 (Box 108, Folder 7)
      - Rosenberg, 1953-1955 (Box 108, Folder 8)
      - Rosenberg, 1956-1957 (Box 108, Folder 9)
      - Rosenberg, James (Box 108, Folder 10)
      - Rosten, Leo (Box 108, Folder 11)
      - Ru-Rz, general (Box 109, Folder 1)
      - Rubicam, Raymond (Box 109, Folder 2)
      - Ruhm, Herbert, #1 (Box 109, Folder 3)